EUR

* BGN
* USD
* EUR
* GBP
* DKK
* MXN
* NZD
* NOK
* PHP
* PLN
* RON
* SGD
* ZAR
* KRW
* SEK
* CHF
* THB
* TRY
* JPY

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

TELEPHONE

* 
* 

LOCATIONS

0.00

Shopping Cart
-------------

0

* * 
    * 

* |

* |
* |
* |
* |
* |

[

ONLINE SUPPORT

Instant support over phone or chat](https://specialneedsequipment.eu/form/1/contact.html)[

EXPRESS DELIVERY

1- day shipments with TNT](https://specialneedsequipment.eu/page/9/delivery.html)[

WARRANTY & SERVICE

Up to 5 years warranty](https://specialneedsequipment.eu/page/10/warranty-and-service.html)[

30-DAY TEST PERIOD

Of non-sanitary products](https://specialneedsequipment.eu/page/1/product-replacement.html)

Accordion Categories
--------------------

Privacy Policy
==============

Global Enterprise ltd. is dedicated to customer support. This policy explains our commitments to you pertaining to how we manage personal data on an ongoing basis.  

**What is Personal Data and why is it important that we have it?  
**  
Personal Data is the information or an expressed opinion through which an individual is identified.  

These include names, postal and electronic addresses, and phone and fax numbers. Personal Data of this kind can be obtained in interview or correspondence, over the phone or via fax, email, through our website www.specialneedsequipment.eu or from third parties – or a combination of any of these. We don’t use cookies on our site. However, we do not guarantee that website links to external sites or our third parties do not use this technology.  

Our primary aim in collecting your Personal Data is the provision of our services and products to you, or of your or general marketing information to our clients, and for the purposes of marketing. We may use your information for ancillary purposes that are directly related to the primary aim, under circumstances of use or disclosure that could be reasonably expected. To remove yourself from updates about our products or associated material, you can simply inform us via email or let us know.  

When it’s possible and appropriate for us to do so, we will inform you why we are collecting your details and what we intend to do with it.  

**Sensitive Information  
**  
Sensitive information relates to data or opinions on an individual such as  
  
\- Race or ethnicity  
  
\- Criminal record  
  
\- Health information  
  
\- Political party, association, trade union or professional body membership  
  
\- Philosophical or religious belief  

The same rules are true for your sensitive information as for your personal data when it comes to the holding of it for the purposes outlined, under permission given by you and in circumstances where it is either required or authorized legally.  

**Third Parties  
**  
We will usually receive any details about yourself from you alone. However, if we receive any information about you from anyone other than you, we will do all we can – within reason – to apprise you of this.  

**Disclosure of Your Data  
**  
Your personal data is subject to disclosure when required or authorized by the law, and to third parties where you approve your data to be used or to be disclosed.  

**Security of Personal Data  
**  
When it comes to data storage, we retain it in a way that means it is protected – within reason – from misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification. In general, most of the personal data we hold will be kept for a minimum of seven years. After the personal data is no longer required for its purposes or the seven year period, we will take reasonable measures to destroy or de-personalize information specific to you.  

**Access to your Personal Data  
**  
You can request access to all the details we hold about you by writing to us free of charge. You may incur a fee for the provision of a copy of those details. We may require confirmation of your identity from you before releasing your details to you.  

**Maintaining the Quality of your Personal Information  
**  
Because keeping your details up to date is important for the provision of our services, it is important that we are apprised of any changes to your information.  

**Updates in Privacy Policy  
**  
In the event of any change to this policy, the policy itself can be found at our office or on the web site to anyone who asks for it.  

**Complaints**  
  
If you wish to lodge a complaint about a breach of our privacy policy, you can contact us.  

**The DPA and GDPR May 2018  
**  
  
We and this website comply with the DPA (Data Protection Act 1998) and with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) which comes into effect from May 2018. We will update this policy accordingly after the completion of the UK’s exit from the European Union.  
  
**The Types of Personal Information We Collect  
**  
We collect information provided to us, such as name, address(es), phone number, email address, payment information (if appropriate) and any other information that you choose to provide to us. In order to safeguard the privacy rights of our patients, we always ask for this set of information with each contact we make. It is very important that when accessing our patient records, we are certain we are looking at the correct file so that, we are only discussing private information with a patient or their representative who has the right to know.  

**How We Use Personal Information  
**  
We use your information in accordance with the data protection principles. We will comply with data protection law. This says that the personal information we hold about you must be:  
  
Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way  
Collected only for valid purposes that we have clearly explained to you and not used in any way that is incompatible with those purposes  
Relevant to the purposes we have told you about and limited only to those purposes  
Accurate and kept up to date  
Kept only as long as necessary for the purposes we have told you about  
Kept securely  

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information  
**  
We may use and disclose Personal Information for the following purposes:  
  
To send you informational and promotional content in accordance with your marketing preferences that you have provided to us. The information is used to generate an email to notify you that it may need replacing when nearing the end of its lifespan. You can stop receiving our promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email.  
  
To send you system alert messages. For example, we may inform you of temporary or permanent changes to our Services, such as planned outages, new features, version updates, releases, abuse warnings, and changes to our Privacy Policy.  
  
To communicate with our members about their account and provide customer support.  
  
To provide, support, and improve the services we offer. This includes our use of the data that our Subscribers provide us in order to enable our Subscribers to use the services.  
  
To provide suggestions to you. This includes adding features that compare what you are searching for and give you options to look at other areas of the website.  
  
To process orders and provide agreed goods and services to you, this may include third party providers for us to process payments that are due to us in order to process sales or provide services on our behalf.  
  
To monitor and/or record conversations to or from you in order to offer you additional security, resolve complaints, improve our service standards and for staff training purposes.  
  
Any Government department, public body, or other third party where we believe in good faith we are legally obliged to do so.  

**Data Retention  
**  
We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.  
  
In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal information so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case we may use such information without further notice to you.  

**Your Rights and Choices  
**  
We want you to be in control of how your personal information is used by us. You can do this in the following ways:  
  
\- You can request a copy of the information we hold about you  
\- You can tell us about any changes to your personal information which we hold  
\- You can ask us to amend any of the personal information we hold about you to ensure it is correct and accurate  
\- In certain situations, you can ask us to erase the personal information we hold about you or request changes to the way we use your information  

During the order process, you will need to give consent for us to use this personal information as detailed. You may withdraw your consent at any time. Where we process your personal information based on legitimate interest or the public interest, you have a right to object at any time to the use of your personal information. In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. To withdraw your consent, please contact info@specialneedsequipment.eu in the first instance. Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.  

**Social and Media Policy and Usage  
**  
We adopt a Social Media Policy to ensure our business, and our staff conduct themselves accordingly online. While we may have official profiles on social media platforms users are advised to verify the authenticity of such profiles before engaging with, or sharing information with such profiles. We will never ask for user passwords or personal details on social media platforms. Users are advised to conduct themselves appropriately when engaging with us on social media.  
  
There may be instances where our website features social sharing buttons, which help share web content directly from web pages to the respective social media platforms. You use social sharing buttons at your own discretion and accept that doing so may publish content to your social media profile feed or page.  

**Email Mailing List and Marketing Messages  
**  
We operate an email mailing list program, used to inform subscribers about products, services and/or news we supply/publish. Users can subscribe through an online automated process where they have given their explicit permission. Subscriber personal details are collected, processed, managed and stored in accordance with the regulations named in ‘The policy’ above. Subscribers can unsubscribe at any time through an automated online service, or if not available, other means as detailed in the footer of sent marketing messages. The type and content of marketing messages subscribers receive, and if it may contain third party content, is clearly outlined at the point of subscription.  
  
Email marketing messages may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of subscriber data relating to engagement, geographic, demographics and already stored subscriber data.  
  
Our EMS (Email Marketing Service) provider is; Mailchimp and you can read their privacy policy in the resources section.  

**How We Use Cookies on Our Website  
**  
  
This website uses cookies to improve the user experience while visiting the website. As required by legislation, where applicable this website uses a cookie control system, allowing Use of Cookies the user to give explicit permission or to deny the use of /saving of cookies on their computer/device.  

**What Are Cookies?  
**  
Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.  
  
Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors or use the cookie control system if available upon their first visit.  

**Website Visitor Tracking  
**  
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.  

**External Links  
**  
Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may, in turn, be saved on your computer’s hard drive. Users should, therefore, note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and we cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.  

**Downloads and Media Files  
**  
  
Any downloadable documents, files or media made available on this website are provided to users at their own risk. While all precautions have been undertaken to ensure only genuine downloads are available users are advised to verify their authenticity using third-party anti-virus software or similar applications.  
  
We accept no responsibility for third party downloads and downloads provided by external third party websites and advise users to verify their authenticity using third-party anti-virus software or similar applications.  

**Changes in Our Privacy Statement  
**  
  
We continually review our practices and will update this policy from time to time.  

**External Website Links and Third Parties  
**  
  
Although we only look to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised to adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. (External links are clickable text/ banner/image links to other websites).  
  
Shortened URL’s; URL shortening is a technique used on the web to shorten URL’s (Uniform Resource Locators) to something substantially shorter. This technique is especially used in social media. Users should take caution before clicking on shortened URL links and verify their authenticity before proceeding.  
  
We cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite our best efforts. Users should, therefore, note they click on external links at their own risk and we cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

**Optimize service and performance tools**

We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices. This includes a device's IP address (processed during your session and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our website. Hotjar stores this information on our behalf in a pseudonymized user profile. Hotjar is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf.  

**Data Protection Compliance  
**  
  
Please contact info@specialneedsequipment.eu if you have any questions about this privacy policy or how we handle your personal information.  

Queries about Privacy Policy  
  
Any queries related to the policy can be directed tous by phone or e-mail:  
  
Tel:  +44 7700015041  
  
E-mail : info@specialneedsequipment.eu

Payment Methods
---------------

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

* 
* 
* 
* 

Copyright 2020 SpecialNeedsEquipment.com

GDPROur website is GDPR compliant.

Opening Hours

Mon-Fri: 09:00 - 18:00

Sat-Sun: 10:00-16:00
